besthostratings.com 2012-09-21

# Privacy Policy - Web Hosting Reviews

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. The following discloses our Privacy Policy.   
**  
What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?**   
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from our site our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We store IP addresses and referrer URL to help detect problems with our server, detect manipulation of ratings, and to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**What are cookies?**  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to detect manipulation of webhost ratings and multiple reviews submissions. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.   
**  
What information do you collect when I rate a hosting company or post a review?  
** In order to submit reviews of a web host, users may choose to include their email addresses, names, and information about their web sites.  This information is not required to add ratings and reviews and users can choose if it will be displayed publicly.  The information collected will not be used for any unsolicited communications or promotional email messages. Furthermore we use special technology to display the user email addreses on our site, so we can prevent harvesting of the latter.     
**  
Webhosting p **lan Submission**  
** Webhosts are required to submit their email addresses, names, and information about their businesses. This information is not displayed publicly.  The information collected will not be used for any unsolicited communications or promotional email messages.  

 **Links** **  
**This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to notice when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site (besthostratings.com).

 **Sharing of information  
** We will disclose personal information and/or an IP address, when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:   
    1)    Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities and conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process.   
    2)   Protect and defend the rights or property of this site  
    3)   Identify persons who may be violating the law

We use reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. We are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information about their users

 **Security**  
We have taken reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  Please remember that no computer system should be considered safe from intrusion.  E-mail may pass through many computer systems, and should not be considered as a secure means of communication unless encrypted.  Access is limited to a very small number of persons with a defined need and is password protected.  If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [webmaster@besthostratings.com](mailto:webmaster@besthostratings.com). 

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions or comments about the Privacy Statement, the practices of besthostratings.com, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [webmaster@besthostratings.com](mailto:security@webhostingratings.com)

 **Notification of Changes** **  
**We reserve the right to change or update the Policy here. If we decide to change our privacy policy, it will be announced on our site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
